{"QandAList":
	[
				{"category":".NET","topic_id":"17","question":"When a new project in Silverlight is created through Visual Studio, how many xaml files are created and what are the uses of those files?","answer":"App.xaml - App.xaml is a file used to declare shared resources like brushes, various style objects etc. and to handle the global application level event (this is almost similar to global.asax file in asp.net application).MainPage.xaml or Page.xaml - This page is the default page of the Silverlight application and when the silverlight application runs this becomes the default page to appear (this page is like the default.aspx page of asp.net application)"},
				{"category":".NET","topic_id":"17","question":"What does XAP mean? ","answer":"XAP is the file extension for a Silverlight-based application package (.xap). This file contains the compressed assemblies and resources of a Silverlight 2 application. "},
				{"category":".NET","topic_id":"17","question":"Can we add the reference of a Class library project in Silverlight application project?","answer":"No, You can't add the reference of a Class library inside the Silverlight application project. You can only add the reference of another Silverlight application project inside a Silverlight application project."},
				{"category":".NET","topic_id":"17","question":"What is the difference between WPF and SilverLight?","answer":"SilverLight is a browser plugin for running it on web where WPF is used for windows application. Though they both make use of XAML.WPF can run as a standalone application(.exe's) whereas Silverlight is implemented by embedding its output in a web page using the proper components. WPF is Windows dependent whereas Silverlight is not Windows dependant. It can be implemented on Linux(MoonLight) and  Nokia's Symbian OS.WPF Can access the database directly whereas Silverlight can't"},
				{"category":".NET","topic_id":"17","question":"What is App.xaml?","answer":"It's a file used in WPF/SilverLight applications to define settings for the different .xaml pages.1) Provides a startup URI in WPF or specify the startup page in SilverLight applications 2)Define event handlers like Application_Error, Application_Startup wherever needed.3)Define global styles inside the resources tag 4)Define properties that can then be used for data passing between .xaml pages."},
				{"category":".NET","topic_id":"17","question":"What is Silverlight.js file?","answer":"It is a helper file which enables Web sites to create advanced Silverlight installation and instantiation experiences. "},
				{"category":".NET","topic_id":"17","question":"Is Silverlight supported in various locales?","answer":"Silverlight installs localized versions of Macintosh computers and Windows. At this time, the installation is available in an international English format. Final releases will render international text (using double-byte characters) and support the full 64K Unicode character set. Silverlight uses simple input mechanism that treats all the languages in the same way."},
				{"category":".NET","topic_id":"17","question":"What are the different ways to display text with Silverlight?","answer":"Silverlight supports displaying static preformatted text that is comprised out of glyph elements and also dynamic text that uses TextBlock. With glyphs, one needs to position the characters individually while TextBlock supports simple layout."},
				{"category":".NET","topic_id":"17","question":"What are the names of main asseblies used by WPF?","answer":"a)WindowsBase b)PresentationCore c)PresentationFoundation "},
				{"category":".NET","topic_id":"17","question":"Describe the types of documents supported by WPF?","answer":"There are two kinds of document supported by WPF a)Flow format:Flow format document adjusts as per screen size and resolution b)Fixed Format:Fixed Format document does not adjust as per screen size and resolution "},
				{"category":".NET","topic_id":"17","question":"What namespaces are needed to host a WPF control in Windows form application?","answer":"a)PresentationCore.dll b)PresentationFramework.dll c)UIAutomationProvider.dll d)UIAutomationTypes.dll e)WindowsBase.dll"},
				{"category":".NET","topic_id":"17","question":"What is Dependency Property In WPF?","answer":"Windows Presentation Foundation (WPF) has a set of services that is used to extend the functionality of a common language runtime property. These services are referred as the WPF property system. A property that is backed by the WPF property system is known as a dependency property."},
				{"category":".NET","topic_id":"17","question":"What is routed event in WPF?","answer":"A WPF user interface is constructed in a layered approach, where one visual element can have zero or more child elements. so we can visualise the elements tree for the full page. Routed events are a new feature provided by WPF which allows events to travel down the elements tree to the target element, or bubble up the elements tree to the root element. When an event is raised, it \"travels\" up or down the elements tree invoking handlers for that event on any element subscribed to that event it encounters en route.This tree traversal does not cover the entire elements tree, only the ancestral element chain between the root element and the element which is the target of the event."},
				{"category":".NET","topic_id":"17","question":"Which class is the base class of all the visual elements of WPF?","answer":"Visual is the base class of all the visual elements of WPF."},
				{"category":".NET","topic_id":"17","question":"What are the Types of controls in WPF?","answer":"Content Control, Item Control, Layout Control"}
	]
}
